大家好
我是小武
今天和大家一同观赏的是
2018年马来西亚公开赛男单决赛
由马来西亚选手李宗伟对阵日本选手桃田贤斗
一比零
双方网前较量调控正手网前抢放逼起球
头顶杀斜线得分
一比二拿都发
后场双方斗网好快推拉开控正手抓过度进攻
平高拉开空往下压
拉都放网踢掉斜线
豪接掉
转对角
抓过度进攻
推球逼过度
头顶突击直线得手
四比三
双方互相控正手
His attack
双方网前较量
操控正手抢放网拿度空头顶滑板
斜线控
正手抓过度下压好抓推
拿都控正手逃过渡斜线
拿都反勾对角侧身突击得分
五比四好网前分球下压拿都接杀转斜线
逃抓推控网抢攻
拿度控
正手抓过度
正手突击斜线得分
六比四曹斜线调动拿都
快推逼过度拿都接杀
转对角逃快推斜线得分
八比六调控转身
空往下压
往前扑压
被防
淘沙上网连贯得分
Uh good attack from the left hander and back hand side
This one that knew the reply
Had to be straight again
七比八逃抓推
双方斗网操控
正手好挡
远网抓推突击得手
八比八拿都分球
抢攻得手
九比八
陶停顿推球
抓推抢搓拿督挑球很到位
逃抓推拿都接杀
高质量挡网得分
Off the body
Look at that off the right
Hit swayed his body out of the way to give himself
A little more freedom to play
十比八调控
正手拿度下压陶连续控
正手拿都吊球
摆脱豪抓过度杀上网连贯得分
Yeah
That's quick
That's the chance to attack that movement to his back
Hand corner
放十比11
Once in a while
双方网前较量调控
正手拿都下压
逃快推拉开
拿都控正手豪华版
吊一拍
空头顶抓过度进攻
拿都控网假杀真吊
秀翻桃田
To disguise
The fact that mama was left absolutely stranded
And that's that's the um variation
14比13陶抓推
拿度回搓
高质量侧身杀
追身得分
14比14逃控正手逃抓推拦截
高点抢放滑板
斜线拿都放远网
抓推得手
15比14好假动作
分球拿都推球
拉开滑板掉一拍
上网跟进好快速把球顶回后场
实现反杀
16比17
拿毒控网抢攻
逃回搓滚网
拿都神级低手位回顾
秀翻桃田
20比17调控正手控网下压
拿督网前扑压得手
拿下了首局比赛的胜利
第二局零比零
双方圆网较量调控
正手抓过度下压拿度往前转
对角调控头顶
拿都连续空转身
朝下压拿督控转身
拿毒高质量推挑使桃田判断失误
一比一拿都空
头顶往前勾
对角头顶突击
直线停顿
推头顶朝下压
操控转身拿都接杀
转对角快推转身抓过度
往前扑杀得分
Against more mortar
But um
二比一调控
头顶拿都滑板
斜线拿都回搓
高质量
起跳重杀带走
Quality of the net plate
Forcing the shortly
豪放网滑板鞋线
空头顶抓摆脱进攻
假放真推得手
二比四拿都停顿
分球调控
正手拿都同样控
正手抓过度劈杀斜线
逃控正手
双方右半区对拉好软压拿督弹
后场破坏连贯
豪放网拿度空
头顶抓摆脱下压控
正手逃过渡后场控头顶抓摆脱进攻双方互相控
正手逃斜线过度高质量推挑选难度
判断失误
五比三淘控正手
拿度空头顶抓过度
劈掉斜线得分
See how much kento more mortis
Overcovering the short forehand corner
八比四跑推挑过顶网前对角变化
拿毒防守反击得分
Oh it's fantastic immediately apologizes
Leeh chong wei for hitting his opponents open the shuttle
Over the neon that block
十比四拿都头顶杀斜线
豪放远网抓推突击得手
And that chara lump
五比十拿都控正手双方圆网控制
拿督再控正手朝斜线过度拿都回勾
好软压空头顶拿都抓
过度劈杀斜线得分好
The motor less stranded ones
At the midgame interval for lee chong
Wei
11比五拿都抓推
曹同样抓推
连续控两底线
抓摆脱进攻
连续控正手
拿都同样连续控正手
往前对角变化
头顶杀直线
豪接杀分
斜线拿都控正手
低手位回勾拿都抓推空转身往前钓鱼得手
And with his back and defense
八比13好抓推
抢搓高质量起跳
重杀得分
十比十
三拿都控网抢攻
双方网前较量调控
转身拿毒
连续控两底线
双方圆网控制操控正手
拿都停顿推挑后场
滑板吊一拍往前扑压桃田
把球快速顶回后场
实现反杀
His foot off the pedal
Hasn't it combine with the fact that
Monala has found his touch at the net
And all of a sudden
I looked very comfortable with a seven point advantage at the
12比13好抓推
拿都同样抓推
陶平高压头顶软压
抓推拦截
拿都弹
后场破坏连贯
网前对角变化
下压抢搓
踢掉斜线好下压拿督弹
后场破坏连贯下压
双方互相控正手
拿都踢掉
斜线控网好
挑球很到位
拿都抓过度进攻
停顿推转身往前钓鱼得分
Equal in the longest rally of the match
So far
13比15毫发
后场拿赌反拍过度
后场抓过度进攻
空网抢攻得手
15比17
双方网前较量
拿度空头顶放网起跳重杀中路得分
16比18好下压
双方往前较量
拿
都抓推
高点放网
好网前对角变化起跳杀球得分
The return is not good enough
And then the attack
他17比18
双方对攻
拿都假杀真吊劈杀斜线
桃田高质量鱼跃接杀挡网
实现反杀
Was actually convinced
It was going to go wide this block
But it was perfect from my motor
19比18拿都往前分斜线下压
拿都控网平高压
头顶双方圆网控制
双方网前较量
调控转身抓过度进攻
空头顶
滑板斜线拿都控网抢攻
连续吊球打中心调动
双方互相控正手
逃抓推拦截
拿毒往前分斜线抓推突击得手
From side to side
Mora rally
No more to match
nineteen19比19调控正手抓过度
往前扑压
双方斗网拿都斜线拉开
控正手双方往前较量
拿都推条很到位
抓过度
劈掉斜线
拿都控网劈掉斜线
好抓推
双方右半区对拉
拿都传统艺能又犯了
Our first challenge of the whole
Match from lee chong wei
And my instinctive reaction
Was it had landed in clearly
And so it is indeed
20比19
拿都空
头顶朝下压逃
抓推拦截
上网跟进
拿都抓推
接杀转对角抓过度
头顶杀大斜线得分
Very positive play from lee chong
Wei dictating the pace of that rally
And an excellent
20比20
桃田网前逼压
被拿督轻松化解
拿都控网抢攻
空转身抓过度下压
拿都控头顶
调控正手拿都过度
后场好软压再控
正手拿都过度
后场控网陶高质量挑球
只拿度
判断失误
It was cool goods
Affected his decision
Making on this one
Ui think it would have been good as well
Yeah
But the indecision casting him
Dear
20一比20拿都分球抢攻
控网朝推球拉开
抓平高进攻
拿都抓推突击得分
20一比21好
假动作分球
往前逼压
被防拿都抓过度
滑板掉一拍控网
踢掉斜线
放网杀
追身好
下压拿都高质量挡网得分
Over
The audience links is uh nut locked skill
You can hear it from the cheer
So having saved to two game point opportunities
Now
李成伟on the22比21曹
连续控正手
抓过度进攻
拿都抓推往前
连续逼压桃田回顶
后场四线判了界内
拿都提出挑战
Ha ha ha h
Well lechon wei dropped his racket to the floor
Thinking
He had won the title
What does haki say
球出界了
拿都赢下了本场比赛的胜利
Okay
I say
What
拿都再一次捍卫了大马的荣耀
获得个人职业生涯的第十个
马来西亚公开赛冠军
What an achievements
By lee chong wei in his fourteenth
Malaysian open final
He wins an incredible twelve title
Great sportsmanship shown by both men
A match played in good spirits
A match played to the very highest quality
Lee chong wei delivering once more in front of his home
Fans
An hour and eleven minutes
Oh simply centilating badminton
Congratulated by henro
One
His coach
Pastein in the very early stages
You said
This is the best quality
Had seen all year
And you weren't sure
Whether it was gonna win that way for what a dramatic final
And it ended that way
Yeah
It ended that way that the
How well
Did he play lee chong wei here
Absolutely amazing
So you got all the statistics
What is
His last victory that is comparable to this one
He said the olympic silver
No
It has to be a a match
Wr
He won the title
Absolutely all england
Probably
There's ukingston there
And terence
Yes
Dad come
And shake
My hand
Ubeautiful moments
Oh you're all sweaty
Daddy
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
That's right after seventy
One minutes